So, you and I are in the middle of perfection
of giving and perfection of giving is very important
for the diamond path, especially for your
diamond path lunches. You need to
practice four types of giving in the
diamond path and this is connected with five
different families. Bud Ratna
Kara is the South,
connected with the color yellow, and there are two
types of giving. Four types of giving are
said there so that you can
penetrate the seed in your consciousness. When you
later take the diamond vows, secret
vows, then you commit to
performing these four types of giving. This is
when we share material things,
and so on.
Then the second type of Kayani that you
commit to performing is called
protection, and all these names of the
four types of giving are secret,
secret, and here protection means
equality, it does not mean to know. People are treated
equally, and it
seems to me that in my
life I rarely meet people of
different races, different genders, or different
countries. I have a
problem. It seems to me that I cannot
treat everyone equally with political
parties, I'm joking, of course. But we are
talking here about equal treatment of everyone
equally. I  I think that we all have
different prejudices and it is important to know that
you have them,
I also think that it is necessary to
monitor
in my
case, and maybe all people have darma,
these are
prejudices of people who
believe in others, have a different
worldview. Therefore, if you want the
diamond path of their okara, then
part of this is accepting
people with different opinions with others with a
different worldview, this is equality
and the third type of giving is ranara - This giving
gift can again be in an
ordinary conversation When you are riding on a
bus and VH,
giving is giving
love, but it also encompasses
itself not from the face and also
includes speaking pleasantly and
truthfully with
people and this is also a type of giving when
we talk about the perfection of giving the
diamond path, this is connected with the Buddha
ranara ratna
kara, you will learn more about this later, I
just sow a seed in your consciousness, so
four types of giving
Let's return to the
text help people in prison, in
prisons, we had  A
very cool project
related to
prisoners. We visited
prisons. There is a prison located
north of
Axon. We also had a center in
Phoenix. It was easy to get there. But
where we are located, it is more difficult to get there. It takes
8 hours to
get there. We don't do this as often
as we did. But we have teachers who
teach there. And here there is a special
point that people in prisons, they especially
suffer very much. People who are prisoners
suffer in America. I think that there is
such a problem. And it seems to me worse than in
other countries. I think we have a
lot of
prisoners. Arizona is one of those
places where they built roles. R because there
was Deya Earth.
Because Earth was cheap and
labor was cheap too. That's why there are
many prisons here. He says that it is
very good karma to communicate with these
people who are in prison. We have been
doing
this for many
years. The person who did this
got cancer and died. So we haven't
done much yet, but it is very
good
karma. My personal experience in
prison is that people are very
grateful to you. People are very
kind.
prison governors
and they They really loved our group
because there were fights Fights became much less so now I'll
show you a really cool one
And tomorrow I'll show you a cool
picture here's a
photo and we had graduates Like
from places of detention,
for example,
Vle And now they've been released are
free Now they have their own
business He says that protecting
people from
danger in
Tibet is For example, when a river
accidentally carries away someone by the current, it's a
temporary disaster If you see
some kind of disaster or incident on the
street, no one
stops But if you are the first one at the scene of an
incident, then Stop and
Help I had a very funny experience
in Ireland I was at the airport in Shen and
I needed to go further than
VGA and I rented a car in
[music] it's
difficult to drive there because on
the contrary
and was ahead of me The car was driving in
Ireland there were huge stones lying
in the fields and they built walls built
walls of stones and on every road There is
such a stone wall and I just drive behind this
car and it starts just hitting
this stone fence  and he's lying
I ran out stopped ran out
of course to the
car there were four
Catholic nuns four in the car I say
you're okay they say We need to go to the
hospital I put them all in my car
it was so funny Because I didn't know
that I they didn't know what kind of monk was
taking them to the
hospital But if you are the first one on the
scene Stop Help
these people and this is also part of giving this is
also a kind of giving the perfection of
giving to you give grant protection And this is
part of ratna kara once you made
a promise in the diamond way you took these
accepted these secret dinners then one of the
greatest gifts you can
give is protection to help people who
are in
trouble and there is a tradition in
Buddhism it is
important and for such a summer retreat which is
held by monks and nuns somewhere 2-3
months in the summer and we go on retreats
mainly and one big reason is because there are a lot of
insects in the summer and you
kill them if you go out here and there and
therefore there is such a tradition in  monks
and nuns often go to these
retreats so as not to walk through the fields and
meadows and not kill
insects. Here he says that we
protect insects from the cold and heat. If,
for example, an insect is drowning, the biggest
thing you can do is save
an insect with just one movement of your
hand, just climb into the water and pull it out. He
says,
don't think that their life is
worth nothing. Their life is also as important to them
as it is to you. Therefore, if you have
the opportunity to save an insect, then do it. He does
n't say that you don't need to
just sit by the lake and constantly fish out
bugs. But if you see that a
bug has fallen into the water, then just pull it out.
Help them. Help them get out.
Help the bugs. When you have such an
opportunity,
then
repeat. And he secretly speaks here
about our secret
dinners. He refers to secret vows.
Because when you give freedom from
fear, this is one of the fourth
types, and he speaks here about this,
this means a lot of tantra, and it is so
veiled
here and to me.  It seems
great when we talk about giving protection
from a strategy
should be done at a
distance
if you have a choke or some kind of
flea on your body that sucks
your blood or a mosquito, this is also a type of giving.
There is such a teacher who says,
I feed mosquitoes, I can’t
do this, by the way, in Arizona, this can be
dangerous, they carry
various diseases, so you don’t have to do this.
In any case, when you have the
opportunity to save any creature, then
do something, don’t be lazy
in the next life, you can be this
bug, just remember
this, and here is a very cool thing,
my grandson taught me this, you
can buy it on Amazon,
it’s very cheap, and also the
production is also
cheap,
and this is a trap. A bug trap. We
use jars to catch a
bug, for example,
flies. It seems I’ve been doing this for 30 years
and they said, “Try it.” This is because
with a ban,
I had a
record of catching many in a
day with a jar, in my opinion, this is all.
A trap is such a vacuum
thing. If you see a spider or see
flies T there
is a special net that gently sucks in
insects. And then you take it outside and
just let it go free and they fly away
and I think this is a very cool thing.
I
like it as if a vacuum cleaner with a sock is
much faster than with a
can and works much better. Sometimes you
can accidentally crush a fly with a can,
but this works great and it's
fun. It seems to me that you are
such a Safari.
I recommend this mate to you. What she
taught me at least. One small movement of your
hand, your small movement of your hand
can save the life of an insect.
When you
practice, when you
perform a
practice. When you
do and
you give someone something with your
breath, for example,
happiness, this is also the perfection of giving.
Performance
in your imagination, in your mind - this is
also perfection. Giving does not
necessarily require giving $100,
$1000. You can simply
share the practice of Tolen with your breath and this is
perfection.
Dani. I like this picture.
Meditation. I worked in Manhattan for almost
20 years and
rose on Manna.
knowledge and
meditated was very cool
feeling during the
lunch break you can take a sandwich with you
go up to the roof of the building a very
beautiful practice turned out But the
best secret practice When you
work on the manne
ra to communicate with
Buddha I will teach
you
come in it is very difficult EVERYTHING there is not
enough time for meditation you work in the
office we were always full of work
and there is no
time closed
there sat down closed the toilet lid
sat on NM And sat there for about five minutes and it seems to
me they thought that I had some kind of problems
with
digestion And I was just doing my
practices just sat and
practiced well It was unpleasant not always
pleasant there smelled Well at least you could be
alone Who is who
and One day I
decided I will I will talk to my future
Buddha and
such Well what Mike Hello what by the way he
never
answers but I am like this I know you
see me future future Buddha can
see
you Teresa future she Buddha can see
you as she sits on the toilet
and
talks to me like this said
hello for too long I hope it will not
take time to become  Budo, do
you have any advice? I'm open to all
advice here because Budo can see the
past, present, future,
and future. She can see you
now. You can talk to her, and it
seems to me that this is very cool. A healthy
way. They can take you by the hand. You can
talk to them. You can talk to them
and ask. Well, how are you doing? Well, I'm
closer to enlightenment. How is my
practice going? I think this is also very
helpful. This is a very
cool practice, so just don't
talk loudly, but you
can. I used it for a huge cost,
and then he
[music]
quotes, and we begin this very
famous book that was written
about 1 year ago. It's a very cool
book
about Translating the EU. Are you interested in Sanskrit?
We also study Sanskrit, if in case
you are interested in studying Sanskrit. I
teach in these classes, and now he will
quote
Ava when we are a
lifestyle guide,
and this is very interesting in the book,
and here is the question of giving - This is perfection.
What is perfection in
Sanskrit? Repeat.
A pair means
left. The English word for exit from this
word happens, it means to leave, to
go away, and  para means on the other
side of the ocean for example like sailing from
Sandiego to Kyoto and this is called
paramita and then he
says giving is paramita Yes
by the way it's not parata
PAZ is perfect they are not
[music]
perfection they lead you to
perfection and the word perfection is the
most famous common
mistake It's not that your
giving is perfect but that your giving
dest who become perfect is not
Six
perfect Who is this to me constantly here on
So he says
giving
dami the perfection of giving
is the perfection of giving we say Yes
Buda taught us this and then someone
says No this is imperfection giving and
we say why is he saying there are still a lot of
poor
people around and that Butoh lived on this planet
Yes did he achieve busti
yes did he perform bu six perfection Yes did
he become did he become perfect in the
first perfection
yes he perfected giving yes Then
why are there so many poor people around and he
We need to talk about what it
means to do perfect giving it
doesn't mean that there won't be any more
poor people around this is what  Your desire to
give the state of Buddhism it has reached
perfection the perfection of giving does not
mean that there will no longer be a desire to
achieve this state Why is everyone
still around Poor people Why is Buddha if
he has mastered the perfection of giving then why are there still
poor people around us
This is happening on their side Yes, this is
happening on their side Buddha cannot
solve your seeds he cannot give you the
seeds of money you must create your own seeds of
money perfect giving but you did not
listen
carefully to his giving it is perfect
but your seeds are your seeds do you really
want to hear something I
cannot give you anything at all when
grandfather gives you 100 dollars who
gives you 100 dollars you give it to yourself the
person who died this
week in the city You must understand what
perfect giving is and you can
be perfect in your giving and there will still be people around
you Poor children you
cannot protect
an insect if it has a
seed you will protect it and if it does not have
this seed When you try  If you
pull it out of the water, you'll just kill it.
You'll sweat it.
If you're trying to save Bug, sometimes you
accidentally
kill it and that's why
perfection It's not that you're protecting
their life, perfection is that you
want to protect their
life You have to
understand this in
Buddhism When you try to help
people, you're limited by their Semina and you have to get
used to this idea and then you
'll talk about I tried to
help three people and they got angry They
said, Go to hell, I
understand, it's normal You're still
giving your perfection, it's still
perfect You can't control the
results of your practice, you can't
When you try to help other people,
you can't control others What will
happen But you have to try Yes, yes,
you have to try to do the
best, of course Will
you always have a great result?
No, of course, we have a lot of problems
here We spent 20 years offering people a
place where they can
go 20 years we worked very hard
and someone is not happy Someone is not
happy Someone is not very good at the time
Leono Nothing else bad we didn't want to
do we tried to help you, so
we can't  control What's
going on What does it mean when you're in the
bass business You shouldn't be upset You
shouldn't
despair Dad he's so
stubborn persistent like Mr.
Bean you're trying to help someone and they're not
happy Well, it's a shame you're not happy but I'll
keep doing
[music]
yat tsya do you sst
can another person sst it's
impossible depends on them but your
responsibility
yours is to do the best and
try to make them sst try
it means don't despair Don't be
upset you can't
control and don't give up
don't give up because
because someone had a bad time and wasn't
happy do the very best to help
others and if they have different seeds then they won't feel
good in and you have to be
patient not create even more
seeds Because these you say well I'm
sorry you didn't like it here we'll try we'll try
you to build next year I'm
very sorry you didn't like the food
I'm very
sorry you got a snake
and
you just can't control
ethos must have an amazing
sense of humor Everything that  Regarding His
practice that today was an unlucky day,
no. So what? Are you going to give up?
Of course not. Well, again on Prota tomorrow.
That's it. Don't be so serious.
You can't
control the seeds that are there.
People will criticize you. Just
help
them. Give them money. Give them
time. You can give it for years, and
people say, "Oh, what kind of food is this, bastard," you
say. Well, okay, let's try
baking tastier donuts next time. That's all when you're
in business. China. You can't. You
can't listen to
the client. Don't despair and don't be afraid.
Just keep helping them. Shut up. Shut up
and keep
helping. Maybe people will thank
you, or maybe they'll curse
you. It doesn't matter what else you should do. Give up.
What about Netflix? Run and watch it.
Yes, I love N. Everything's
great. I like Korean soap
operas. Well, after an hour, I
get bored. How much can you watch? And
then you come back to
be a whale again. This is the
best. You can't measure success
[music] by
some kind of economic level of the country.
This isn't here.  no connection It depends
on the people who live in this country
and it's not about Buddha, you can't judge. You can't judge.
What is the current
economic situation in the country?
M.
Help, if the measure of success of Buddhist
practice is something, then the world is changing for
other people who don't practice,
then it's
crazy, even practice doesn't
mean that they don't keep their
giving. Buddhists who are not
bass are still generous, but you can't
judge. If you see bad things there,
for example, the state of the economy around, it
depends on the people
around. I have a g. I think he
told this story and he passed away.
By the way, I had a Christian friend. We
grew up together since the third grade.
We met together when we were 8 years old. And
now we were about 60 years old and I
invited him to just hang out with
me for a day or two. I came from
Phoenix and we had a very interesting
conversation. He is such a
very good Christian. I
go and
visit. When I was little, I
sneaked into his church's Bible study classes
and we talked for a very long time
and he said, "I'm
worried about all this stuff."  with
your bahi I just said
Why the theory
[music]
to collect good seeds and live in
such a bubble their life will be very
cool very beautiful and all the people
around him suffer it turns out
He go your
religion you say that pohi satva
accumulates good seeds and then pohi
he lives again in this paradise
bu and other people around them they have
SG and all that oh got I like this
idea I told him And what is your idea
about
this and then you hear such strange
things that there is someone who makes you
suffer someone created you and then
someone is the reason that you
get cancer I say that since
this bubble is better than my
bubble and he
says I think that yes we are
in a certain bubble
and you can reach
out You
can help people sow cool
seeds You can give a gift but you
cannot control their bubble e once pov Yes
ihr also happens correctly
such remnants of
greed When you did not want to share
your
pleasure perfection giving is a
mental Practice is not a physical
practice This desire is what
You have this, there is the perfection
of giving,
all
the conditions, the seeds of another person can
be Note that so that he receives your
generosity But the main thing is your desire to
give, this is your desire and not the success of the
giving itself. Here they
gave 1000 dollars and someone invested it,
for example, I don’t know, in nuclear
development, we don’t know, you just have to
try Do your best and be a
generous person and help others, but you
cannot predict What people will do with
it So it doesn’t work, it
means strengthen your ability, your
desire to share, and this is your
perfection You cannot control
what the world does You cannot
control what people do When
you give, you just have to continue to
give with
wisdom, especially for example when we don’t
share drugs or weapons, don’t
give, don’t give those things that
hurt others, that harm
Therefore, try to
do I know I know rich parents
who give too much to their children and
then these children become useless,
they can’t do anything It’s about the
amount of
growth of
giving, he
says again, he turns to the
monk, which
means
parts of a monk’s
robe,
skirts, T, a poor man, and says I
need I need  clothes You must be
ready to give this is the readiness to
give this is the perfection of giving
Should a monk give his robes to
another person they say no no he shouldn't
I gave When someone was
cold I remember we were walking somewhere I
gave
shared Roy But usually you shouldn't
give your Rob
But you must be ready to give your
desire are you ready do you have
the desire and well l  and this No, it's not
good, start with small
things, let's take it
easy, he says, start with vegetables, in
my case it's not difficult at all.
Last night I gave away only
vegetables, they come back on a plate in time,
they say with small
things, just learn, learn to
give small things and then
expand, start with small,
you can even give part of your body,
start with small things, give
small things throughout the day, share
this and then you can give your
body. You can strengthen, increase your
generosity
by giving, starting with small things,
start giving small things on an
ongoing basis. The
next picture. It seems to me that
this is yes, it's
difficult to find dead people online,
MRI photos, people don't want to post such
photos, we will all
die, we can't, we
can't keep everything
you have.
I have a very cool, cool, cool
diamond ring, I carry it
with me in my purse, and someone told their
ten-year-old child, I think maybe I should
give him this
ring. I
gave it and then I'll regret it,
maybe my wife will be upset,
and then I
thought if I keep it, I
still won't be able to keep it, I'll die, and it will
remain in
Maybe it will go to my purse When I
die when he will clean out my purse
someone will still be there maybe I should
give it away for now when I have
things that I have
for example
Give it to
someone maybe tomorrow I will crash In a
car accident we don’t
know Give it to someone Before it’s too
late when you die when you
die you won’t be able to take anything with
you so
Give it do something
good Before it’s too
late and then someone will do something for
you By the
way when you give away your things you
feel free yourself free I have
nothing and I gave away everything good
only the guitar is
left just give it away give it away while you
have the chance be happy while you have the
chance By the way Well when you
have to clean up all this afterwards people get
annoyed why did you go all this junk I
kept now I have to clean it all up
it annoys other people there are such
Believe
me if you make it a habit
travel light through life you will be
much happier Put away all your things
rid yourself of these
things that I have Lord a pair of
underwear three pairs of
shoes three t-
shirts and the rest is all Give it away
Keep yourself the bare minimum and you will be
much happier If you
travel, it
will be much easier for you to give,
don't be content, don't
be content with what you give out,
keep giving, keep
giving if someone asked you for something,
give, just
give, and now
we have advice on almsgiving,
yes, when it's printed in small letters in a contract
if you have nothing to
give and you have such a desire to
earn money, exchange money,
give
more donations, make Latin
America, maybe I can cheat with
taxes, he says, no, no, this is no longer the
perfection of giving,
this is no longer considered
generosity. When you do something
dishonestly and then give it away, this is the
wrong approach. It's better then to
give nothing at all.
Again, his
audience was monks,
and he got into trouble. Yes, he got into trouble
because he taught ordinary people, he was
criticized, you can still read
in books that people were
already dying, but he was so heavily
criticized because he taught ordinary
people.
The first three
perfections are especially good for the world,
which are neither  monks monks
Why is it easy to give because Mona
monk has practically nothing, it is not
allowed
that they have
Then it is more possible to be these And the
third
is patience there is such a joke in
tek not
[music]
I know that much more patience is needed
when you are not Mona
in the monastery There is enough inside too
And this is a quote from where to
harm which I will teach you after
we are in December I hope After December
and Master
Chandra says the first three
perfections are good for
laymen there are certain Gifts things
that you should not give until you are at a certain
level for example When you can give
your
body to give your life for another person
losing this
body does not
mean body parts are
possible The main thing is that you do not die in the process,
but if you die for someone we are not yet at
that level we are not yet
strong enough for this
than you do not give away your body until you have
it ALL you still
need on such a day perhaps When you
When you reach that level but we are
not yet and every time the Lama
says You have not reached
this level And I tell you
no he said
it will be You are eating wrong  your
body in this mo at this level
he says you are not allowed to give
your body away. You must take care of
yours. You have a responsibility to
take good care of your body, eat well,
exercise, and take care of your body as soon as
you
are in business. Your body
already belongs to other people, so
you have no right to harm your body,
overdo it, or, conversely, not give
it enough exercise. This body is no longer
yours. It does not belong to you. You have already made
a promise to serve other people and you
have a moral responsibility to be
healthy. The day will come when you
can give away your body. It will be
as easy as giving away fat, for example.
He says. Then you can safely
do it, but we are not ready for you yet. By the way,
people who tried
to do it were just showing off, trying to
brag. In fact, they are
not ready. They can cut off a finger.
He says, listen. Keep your fingers to
yourself. You will need them. Take better
care of yourself. Don't brag that you
can
do such great things. It's just
x. How great when the best thing is when your
grandfather has it, it seems to me, a lot of
history. We studied the life of Milarepa in
New Jersey When I lived in a Mongolian
monastery in the temple there was a young
man we were studying life in the
world of re street in the forest and this young
man he
immediately gave all his
things
and went into the forest burn I will live like
Milarepa and it got cold immediately ran
back as soon as it got cold It was
so
funny And forget about
it and I once stayed in a cave and
decided that I would meditate there at
night such thousands of spiders I was like
so Perhaps I will return to a better
booth there will be at least a door
and now he will talk about things
that are not quite good done
for a monk or for a nun to give away
their robes
to sacrifice Well, maybe of course the case
if someone dies from the cold For example,
can I make
an announcement
Tomorrow is tomorrow or today
and
when can we talk about it Well,
okay 545 will be
initiation you will find out who it is when you
come if you are interested
to see how monks visit a novice, then
you can
join will accept Moshe
I have an opinion if people want Ask
sweat I think
that the person he should
just  clothes
haircuts he should stand out for his
ethics morality his
integrity in my
opinion You should say that this
person is a monk or monks Not
because of his haircuts and not for his
clothes but because he is very kind and he is
very eze
monks dress based on his behavior on
his ethics and not on external
vi because even here robes Iriska
on the contrary they are
distracting in the modern
world old times It's just that we had something
connected that you can't have sex
if lo
our modern ra times it's very
distracting when a person walks roh him
Kato special
hairstyle I think that people just few
people will talk to them with such
people I saw Western monks nuns
they look strange no one wants to
talk to them and they can't
teach other
people I feel that For example, if
you ask me to give these
vows to someone if you are of course interested in my
opinion
just even your parents won't
talk to you you will go to ro podst
But if you want to do this but yes if
you want Grandfather you
by I am not selling not  I sell,
I trade in behavior,
morality, morality, and I
think that a monk or nun should
stand out from the crowd with their
behavior and not their
appearance. This is what I propose for me.
In any case, it is
good
when monks do not give away their
robes. Well, if someone does not freeze from
the cold, does not die from the cold, then you
can of course give away your monastic
robes. And he says you also it is not very
good to give, for example, some food to
monks or nuns
because they, well, after lunch, for example, yes,
because they must collect in this
tradition, the tradition in which I was raised.
When you become a monk or
nun, you are given a choice. You
can not eat after lunch. And I kept this
lunch for 15 years. I did not eat after lunch.
There
was
food.
Because I had such a
schedule with yoga, I had to eat,
so I changed my
habits, my diet. And in this tradition, an
ancient tradition, a monk or nun
should not eat after
lunch. In this tradition, when you are
ordained and you receive vows, you Dat
You are given a choice either you can keep them for
one day or throughout your entire life,
but I
believe
I am not eating anything until 12 o'clock now, I think
this is a very good healthy
habit, it also helped me in my
career in business, I did not
eat, I did not eat after all of my
corporate
career, after this it
helped me and really helped keep my
mind very clear, but to decide
there and he says monks and monks and not
monks and monks
they are not
allowed to
eat garlic and
onions
because it will be inappropriate to teach to offer to offer
onions and
garlic and they say that there are special
animals that live in these, for example, in vegetables
that grow underground, they do not
eat potatoes, they eat
onions, radishes, for example, because you can
kill all these little
creatures to give something inappropriate,
inappropriate to a person from another religion.
This is also not entirely correct. This also
will not be considered the perfection of giving.
Chiva
says some unpleasant smelling
in the
monastery you live very close to
other people in large numbers, you
debate every day for 3 to 4 hours and
this  It
is inappropriate to eat garlic or
onions because everyone will suffer as soon as
you start, and as soon as your breath
starts, your frills will fall off. They
just say that they don't eat
very strong food with a smell.
When you
offer writing to someone who
especially has
the intention to criticize this, it is
considered, for example, you give
someone a cut who intends to, who
has the
intention, it's just a
complex expression. It means
to die, it means to want to have a
desire. This can
mean helping a person who wants to
harm another, therefore, it is considered
inappropriate, for example,
to sell alcohol, weapons, trade in
weapons and give such inappropriate,
incorrect things that will
harm others. Or, for example,
things that encourage a person
to commit
suicide. Well, for example, yes. If you, you
will not be considered bad. If you
refuse to give someone a weapon or poison,
then you do not break your vows under the
pistol. You can buy me a gun so
that I
commit suicide. Yes, you should
give, but buy me a gun so that
I shoot, of course, and therefore this does not
mean that  you must give everything if
it will harm someone, then of course you
should not do
this and of course you
should not share the secret teachings with
those people who are not yet ready or
who have not been initiated into these
secret teachings.
Two terrible things happened to this. No,
nightmares. I don’t remember
ever having a nightmare. I have a
friend who just has the same nightmare every day. I’ve
never had this before,
but this week, twice at once,
and I was so
surprised. And it was
I had nightmares about
people who practice Tant
inappropriately, who do not follow the
rules of
tantric and teach people Tant. These
were two terrible
nightmares, so you must know that you
must know the rules to share the
diamond path with other
people.
If you received a secret teaching from
your grandfather, then your grandfather’s policy is that you must
complete 18 courses before
taking the secret
teachings. I tried and there were exceptions and
they all failed, all of them, so
please do not give people the secret
teachings until they have completed 18.  courses,
this is
grandfather's request and do not look for anything on the Internet, there
are 18 tantric courses
here, the best tantric courses in the world.
They are the best in
history and they are about 20,000 pages. You
can spend your whole life and you do not
need to look for something on the Internet and
get some incomprehensible knowledge
that does not belong to some other
line of transmission. You do not need to do this if
you
finish, cover these 20,000 pages,
then tell me if you need more.
Understandably. And I will check all your homework,
by the way, for starters. And then I will give you more
strange things, but do not waste your
time. This is the
Diamond course that we have. It is complete in
the history of Buddhism in this
world. It is pure and very purified.
Clear, very beautiful and this is a beautiful,
incredible practice. So do not waste
your
time so that I do not have nightmares at night.
These would be terrible dreams when people
receive them. They are just like people who got into a
rad because they practiced incorrectly.
You do not need to do this.
Take these.  20,000 pages If you are
still not satisfied with everything Find
me I will give you even more material even
stranger more strange
things online A lot of this is
inappropriate these are incorrect things this is
not
diamond that's what you
call out
nothing but
and this is a lifelong practice You can
practice your whole life and you will not even
get to the end the end will still be very
far away so it's not the business of
countries so that
grandfathers at least some hair remains on the head
and so here in general Why not
teach deep teachings to people who have not
completed their 18 courses this is called, they say, the
wrong people
inappropriate people I tried It
seemed to me I met people who were
special and it all ended in
disasters
therefore Complete your 18
If you cannot complete them then you will
not have success on the diamond path if you
say This is too much work you will not be
able to complete the tantric
path so Do not
engage in is this activity
Lord
to send criminals to freedom no they should they
should be tried according to the laws of the country
and kept in special institutions I
will not
add anything else this does not mean that this is
kindness  What
you do is not considered kindness, what do
you mean by going and releasing
all the jurims from harming other people?
If we can help
them in some way, then yes,
go to prisons, teach them.
Dedicate your whole life to this, teaching
people in prison, and do this for 5-6 years.
If there are people who want to be
released, then help them. But
this does not mean that you should
release all the jurims, all the criminals, because
this will cause harm. There are
certain
objects in life that you
should not offer to people, for example, people who
want drugs or to kill themselves. If you are a
bai, this does not mean that you give
everything away. It means that you take
responsibility to give what is
appropriate without
any doubt.
I know you are tired, that it is difficult to take
two classes in a row like this, but
just stay with me. I swear to you that when I
cooked in India, my
students suffered even more.
Never, never
give away what you get in such
relationships. And
part of the
ingredient is what you get. What you get is what you get
back much more. It's
great that you think so. No, if
for example, I give 1,000 dollars Then I will
receive, for example, 100,000 dollars and then
I can give even more And it's great to
think so
We have 3 minutes so
stay
with
us and here we talk about the
morality of giving And when you
make difficult decisions like
that You must sometimes make very
difficult decisions When you have, for example, a
lot of
money, you can give Money to good
decisions that you make To whom you will
give it
money is
also a way of life we ​​didn't just throw it around
asked the teacher there are so many
homeless people should help everyone he said
No he said Do your
best You don't have to
use go out you can help for
example children build a
school you have to make a
decision all the time we don't have unlimited
unlimited resources Give someone
something to everyone Give something but you still have to
How to sign up to make
a decision Where to give your money and this is
also part of being Bachi Savoy there
are such difficult decisions To whom to
give
This is a big problem
to make these decisions with
joy and you must make
decisively like for example a surgeon who
needs to cut or
excise something You must be
tough Denmark And it won't be
wrong to
say
about something, some
reports You have to be tough, that is, it's
normal to ask for some reports
because you are responsible for it
I will donate to your
project, but I want to see the reports I want to
see all the receipts and accounting documents
For example, paying taxes so that everything is
clean for you, all your accounting is
clean if there is something wrong, then of course
I'd rather give the money to someone else and
therefore when he
gives it, he must be responsible and
take responsibility Yes, I will donate to
your cause, but I must be sure that
you use this money correctly And
that's
right, he is in the
ass, it's not so easy for him to
donate money to you because you
have to
prove to him that you are worthy of it And how
tough should you be
When you give your
money, the
last thing
was the company We had a turnover of
about
300,000 diamonds per day, just like that, diamonds,
diamonds, they are just
[music]
everywhere, we are everywhere, they were just
lying like that
and I talked to  with my business
partners and they asked me, "
Listen, mom, you have a kind heart, you
trust
everyone, but don't do anything, don't create
conditions for people to steal. Because you're
causing
harm, not everyone is noble. There are
security guards all around.
He should also
respect other people's property and
should
also not create conditions for people to
steal because they will cause harm to a
person.
No, for this responsibility,
to protect other people from
themselves. Therefore, when you're in business, dad, I've
learned a lot for many days. And I thought about this. I don't like not
trusting people. Let these diamonds
lie here," he says, "Don't do
this, don't do it like that." How briefly. This is
a misfortune on their heads, so
subscribe. He shouldn't create
such conditions for people to
harm each other because they can't
control themselves.